m6m.com 2013-09-23

# privacy policy - m6m Games

**m6m.com privacy policy**

* How your personal Information is used 

We use your email address to send you your password. This is also applicable should you use the lost password or lost username feature on the site. We may also from time to time send you emails about offers or updates with m6m.com . We do not pass any personal information (including email addresses) to 3rd parties. Information pertaining to the age is of essential value in identifying the minors, who need to obtain permission from parents or from their legal guardian to get registered as a member of m6m.com (Minors present in the United States are the children who get categorized under 13, and in the non-US countries, children under the age of 16 years get categorized as minors) 

* IP address and logging

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting patterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). Third Party Advertising  
We may use Google Adsense and/or other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit m6m.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you 

* Cookies

Some ads displayed may come from our servers. Ads loading from our servers may also contain cookies, the purpose of these cookies is just to introduce and select the proper advertisements to be shown for your interests. We only have access to information of visiting frequencies of our visitors from cookies you might receive while viewing ads from our servers. 

* Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

* Parental Rights

As a parent you have the right to request all personal information stored about your child on our servers. At your request we will provide this information to you within 7 working days. 

* Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the terms in this policy at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to ensure you are upto date with contents of this privacy policy.
